{
    "question": "Soba is a small town in my country,Sudan.It is 15 kilometres from Khartoum,The Capital of Sudan.The Nile River flows through Soa.That makes the green and beautiful.Most of\u00a0 the pople in Soba works as farmers or a fisherman.The Nile is very important in their lives.A small market in Soba sells food to the people who cannot go to the market in the capital. In Soba,a small hospital and a pharmacy gives medicine to the people without money.About 50 percent of the people in Soba work in the hospital.The youth a place to meet every night except Friday. Friday is a holy day in Soba,so the people go to the mosque,and they say their prays.The people in Soba love their town.They are very happy because Soba is crowded with beautiful things. \u00a0 Question 1.What is the text talking about? 2.What is the suitable title for the text?\r\n 3.What is the function of the text?\r\n 4.When is holy day in Soba?\r\n 5.Where is Soba located?",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "1. Soba<br>2. Soba Town<br>3. to describe Soba more specific\u00a0<br>4. On Friday<br>5. 15 kilometers from Khartoum, the capital of sudan (:",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "saya-ingin-tau-cerita-apa-saja-tentang-fairy-tale-785",
            "question": "Saya ingin tau cerita apa saja tentang fairy tale ?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span><span><span><br></span><span>Fables, Fairy Tales, Stories andNursery Rhymes</span></span><span><span>Aesop&#039;s Fables<span><span>The Ass in the Lion&#039;s SkinThe Bat and the WeaselsThe Fox and the HedgehogThe Fox and the LeopardThe Fox and the MonkeyThe Lion, the Fox, and the AssThe Monkey and the CamelThe Mouse, the Frog, and the HawkThe Sick LionThe Tortoise and the Hare</span><br></span>Hans Christian Andersen<span><span>The Beetle who went on his TravelsThe Emperor&#039;s New ClothesThe Little MermaidThe Princess and the PeaThe Snow ManThe Snow QueenThumbelina or Little TinyThe Ugly Duckling</span><br></span>Grimms Fairy Tales<span><span>Beauty and the BeastCinderellaGoldilocks And The Three BearsHansel and GretelLittle Red Riding HoodSleeping BeautySnow White and the Seven DwarfsThe Three Little PigsThe Wise Little Girl</span><br></span>Lewis Carroll<span><span>Alice&#039;s Adventures in WonderlandThrough the Looking Glass</span><br></span>Carlo Collodi<span>Pinocchio<br></span>Mother Goose and Selected Nursery Rhymes<span>Baa Baa Black SheepHey Diddle DiddleLittle Boy BlueLittle Miss MuffetMary Had A Little LambOld MacDonald had a FarmRing-a-Round a RosieThere Was An Old Woman Who Lived In A ShoeThree Little Kittens</span></span><br></span><br></span>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "fairy tale adalah cerita dongeng yang tidak nyata.ada banyak kisah yg tidak nyata di Indonesia seperti: Gunung Tangkuban perahu, Asal mula danau toba, Batu belah batu betangkup dll",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "gimana-ya-cara-buat-soal-yang-kyak-gini-make-sentences-using-879",
            "question": "gimana ya cara buat soal yang kyak gini.. \u00a0 MAKE SENTENCES USING THE WORDS PROVIDED. READ THE SENTENCES ALOUD. \u00a0 ex : agus/not/like/comics \u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 agus doesn t like comics \u00a0 \u00a0 1.leo/need/a compass/? 2.we/not/like/jazz music",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "leo is not need a compass<br>we are not like jazz music<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "1. Leo need a compass<br>2. We don&#039;t like jazz music<br><br>Contoh soalnya<br>1. Agus/not/study/for exam<br>2. Ingga/do/playing/football<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-opini-setuju-dengan-adanya-saving-a-parkland-861",
            "question": "Contoh opini setuju dengan adanya saving a parkland.",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "\"i agree to save the parkland, because it will be very good to save the nature. beside that, park is a place where children play. we dont want to ruin their happiness:D and beside that, we can even do a picnic in a park. so, we must stop destroying a parkland. it will be useful in another day\"<br>semoga membantu:D<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "i agree to save parkland,cause parkland usually made as a oxigen producers of a big city ,a parkland can make a\u00a0ton of oxygen so parkland must build in the centre of the city to absorb the carbon dioxide and produce oxigen",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buat-conveying-exciting-news-851",
            "question": "Buat conveying exciting news\u221b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Convey artinya adalah menyampaikan sehingga conveying exciting news artinya menyampaikan berita yang excited<br><br>Contohnya adlaah\u00a0<br><br>Ladies and gentleman, I am glad to announce you that the highway which is connecting Java and Sumatra Island has been done. So from now on we could expect that the development in Java can contagious to Sumatra.\u00a0<span></span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "jawaban-dari-the-childern-love-cartoon-movies-703",
            "question": "Jawaban dari \r\n\"the childern love cartoon movies, ..... ?\"",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "the children love cartoon movie, don&#039;t they?<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<strong>anak anak suka film kartun</strong>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "complete-the-short-text-with-the-correct-words-from-the-box-this-517",
            "question": "Complete the short text with the correct words from the box!    This is my 1)____.she is 2)___policewoman.she 3)____\"The Police are Kids Best Friends\". 4)____. She explains the 5)____.the 6)___know the traffic signs,so they can\u00a0be careful on the road. she protect the town 7)____crime. In 8)____spare time,she takes 9)____to 10)____cinema.\r\n\r\na. the\r\nb. her\r\nc. mother\r\nd. program\r\ne. students\r\nf. the\r\ng. traffic signs\r\nh. from\r\ni. me\r\nj. joins",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>This is my 1)__<strong>C</strong>__.she is 2)__<strong>F</strong>__policewoman.she 3)__<strong>J</strong>__\"The Police \nare Kids Best Friends\". 4)__<strong>D</strong>__. She explains the 5)__<strong>B</strong>__to.the 6)__<strong>E</strong>__know \nthe traffic signs,so they can\u00a0be careful on the road. she protect the \ntown 7)__<strong>H</strong>__crime. In 8)__<strong>B</strong>__spare time,she takes 9)_<strong></strong>_<strong>I</strong>__to 10)__<strong>A</strong>__cinema.<strong></strong></span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "1. mother. 2. the 3. joins 4. program 5. traffic signs 6. students. 7. from 8. her 9. me 10. the",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "arrange-the-following-jumbled-words-into-correct-senteces-1-use-774",
            "question": "Arrange the following jumbled words into correct senteces.    1. uses - butcher - to - knive - cut - meat - the.\r\n2. has - cow - farmer - a - the - field - the - rice - plow - to.\r\n3. his - picture - with - takes - camera - photographer - a - the.\r\n4. a policeman - civilians - protects - the.\r\n5. doctor - helps - take care - a nurse - to - patiens - the.\r\n6. the - write - uses - typewriter - writer - to.\r\n7. sends - by - a - letters - postman - motorcycle.",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1. Butcher uses knife to cut the meat<br>2. The farmer has a cow to plow the rice field<br>3. The photagrapher takes a picture with his camera<br>4. A policeman protects the civillians<br>5. A nurse helps the doctor to take care patients<br>6. Writer uses the typewriter to write<br>7. A postman sends letters by motorcycle",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "materi-tentang-giving-attention-the-speaker-please-dong-756",
            "question": "Materi tentang Giving, Attention the speaker????\r\n\r\n\r\nPlease dong......!!!",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span><span>Giving Attention</span><br>1.\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0The Definition of Gaining AttentionGaining attention is a way or expression that is spoken so that other people will pay their attention to what we want to.2.\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0Expressions We Can Use to Ask Other People Attention\u00a0Here are some expressions we can use to ask aother people attention.1)\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0Attention, please!2)\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0May/can I have your attention, please?3)\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0Look!4)\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0Look here!5)\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0Excuse me!6)\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0Excuse me, look here!7)\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0Listen to me, please.8)\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0Waiter?9)\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0I\u2019m sorry, but \u2026.10)Wow, really?11)Excuse me, look here, please.12)I\u2019m listening.\u00a0Example :\u00a0<span>\u00a0Some of the examples by which you can showcase your keen attention to detail to the interviewer are:<br>1.\u00a0Talk about job role specifications and try understanding the deliverables. Ask questions.<br>2.\u00a0Try exhibiting your knowledge about the organization, the teams involved, the current market scenario and how the organization is trying to tackle the situations.<br>Lack of attention to detail<br>Lack of attention to detail is not really a good trait.<br>In fact, it is something that most of the employers look down upon. After all, no one wants to hire a lazy bum who pays no\u00a0attention to details!<br>How to improve attention to details<br>Anyone can improve his/her attention to details. All that is required is an intent and focus to achieve it. Perhaps, the best way to develop the trait is to start paying attention to things around you</span></span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "make-a-dialogue-using-1asking-and-giving-2present-continous-t-824",
            "question": "Make a dialogue using :    1.Asking and giving \r\n2.Present continous tense\r\n3.Simple present tense\r\n4.Singular form\r\n5.Plural form",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Simple Present Tense<br>Habli : do you always breakfast every morning?<br>Dirga : yes i always breakfast every morning.",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-ceritakan-kembali-cerita-di-bawah-ini-240",
            "question": "Tolong ceritakan kembali cerita di bawah ini !    \u00a0\r\n\r\n \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 The greedy dog\r\n\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 One day, a dog stole a big piece of meat and he was very\r\n proud of it. Then, he ran off until he reached the bank of the river. He looked\r\n down into the river water carefully and he saw another dog with a piece of meat\r\n in its mouth.\r\n\r\n\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 Funnily enough, the dog did not realize that it was his own\r\n reflection\u00a0 in the water. When he was\r\n full, he threw himself on the other dog to steal his meat as well.\r\n Unfortunately, when he was in the water, he had to let go the remains of the\r\n meat to avoid drowning, and so was left with nothing.",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Anjing yang serakah<br><br>suatu hari si anjing mencuri daging yang sangat besar, dan ia bangga karna itu. Lalu ia berlari sampai ia menapai sungai yang besar. Iamelihat ke air sungai dengan hati-hati. Lalu ia melihat anjing yang di mulutnya terdapat daging yang besar.<br>Lucunya, si aning tidak menyadari bahwa itu adalah pantulan dirinya sendiri.<br>Saat ia penuh, ia melempari dirinya sendiri ke anjing lainnya untuk mencuri daging milik si anjing itu. Sayangnya saat di air, ia melepaskan sisa-sisa daging agar tidak tenggelam. Jadi yang tertinggal tidak ada apa-apa<br><br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}